{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"9.0.2","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":3879,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":19,"width":1024,"height":627,"responsive":false,"scalable":true,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Text_Caption_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1","title":"Le Café Français ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_2","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si11944","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si11958","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide5303","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_1","Button_2","si11944","si11958"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":630},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5303"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_1","title":"Bonjour! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_2","title":"Salut! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_35","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_37","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_37","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide5375","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_1","SmartShape_2","Image_35","Image_37"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":420},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5375"}}},{"id":"Image_55","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_55","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_19","title":"Recognize basic French salutations Recall the French words for basic café foods & drinks Apply module language to real-world situations  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_20","title":"Upon completion of this module, you will be able to: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12266","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_55","Text_Caption_19","Text_Caption_20"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":681},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12266"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_3","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14135","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14145","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_4","roles":{}},{"id":"si13770","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_4","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14157","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14167","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_5","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_5","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14179","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14189","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_10","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_6","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_28","title":"Click any button to attempt a challenge & win drapeau points ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_33","title":"Simple ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_34","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_34","title":"Moyenne ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_35","title":"Difficile ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"QuestionFlag5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"QuestionFlag5","roles":{}},{"id":"si15578","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si15611","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"QuestionFlag6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"QuestionFlag6","roles":{}},{"id":"si15626","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si15659","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"QuestionFlag1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"QuestionFlag1","roles":{}},{"id":"si15674","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si15707","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"QuestionFlag2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"QuestionFlag2","roles":{}},{"id":"si15722","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si15755","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"QuestionFlag3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"QuestionFlag3","roles":{}},{"id":"si15770","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si15803","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"QuestionFlag4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"QuestionFlag4","roles":{}},{"id":"si15818","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si15851","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si15931","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si15945","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide5506","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_3","si14135","si14145","Image_4","si13770","SmartShape_4","si14157","si14167","Image_5","SmartShape_5","si14179","si14189","Image_10","Image_6","Text_Caption_28","Text_Caption_33","Text_Caption_34","Text_Caption_35","QuestionFlag5","si15578","si15611","QuestionFlag6","si15626","si15659","QuestionFlag1","si15674","si15707","QuestionFlag2","si15722","si15755","QuestionFlag3","si15770","si15803","QuestionFlag4","si15818","si15851","Button_4","si15931","si15945"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5506"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_33","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15070","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15080","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_64","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_64","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_25","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_25","title":"Oui oui! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13418","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_33","si15070","si15080","Image_64","Text_Caption_25"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13418"}}},{"id":"Image_32","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_32","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_34","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_34","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_18","title":"Bonjour! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide5621","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_32","Image_34","SmartShape_18"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":144},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide5621"}}},{"id":"si1703","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13809q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13819","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13809q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13930","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si13846","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Ready? On-y va! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13853","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"What is the French word for hello? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13868","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13872","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"¡Holà! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13868_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"¡Holà!\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13879","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13883","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Bonjour! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13879_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Bonjour!\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si13926","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si13934","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide13809q0","for":"Slide13809q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13948","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide13809q0","for":"Slide13809q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13962","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide13809q0","for":"Slide13809q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13887","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Très bien fait! You are correct - click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13809q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13900","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Désolée, you are incorrect - click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13809q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13913","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Attends! Wait! You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13809q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13809","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1703","si13819","si13846","si13853","si13872","si13883","si13934","si13948","si13962","si13913"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13809"},"question":{"interactionId":"13833","quizId":377,"title":"Ready? On-y va!\r","text":"What is the French word for hello?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["2"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si13986","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13976q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_29","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_29","title":" ¡Adiós! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_30","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_30","title":"Sayonara! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_31","title":"See you later! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_32","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_32","title":"Aurevoir! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14077","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si14006","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Farewell! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14013","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Which word is used to say goodbye in french? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14020hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_4","roles":{}},{"id":"si14020","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si14073","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si14081","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide13976q1","for":"Slide13976q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14095","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide13976q1","for":"Slide13976q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14109","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide13976q1","for":"Slide13976q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14034","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Très bien fait! You are correct - click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13976q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14047","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Désolée, you are incorrect - click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13976q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si14060","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Attends! Wait! You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13976q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13976","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1703","si13986","Text_Caption_29","Text_Caption_30","Text_Caption_31","Text_Caption_32","si14006","si14013","si14020","si14081","si14095","si14109","si14060"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13976"},"question":{"interactionId":"14000","quizId":377,"title":"Farewell!\r","text":"Which word is used to say goodbye in french?\r","type":"graded","ikc":false,"interactionType":"hotspot","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["0"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_34","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_34","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15092","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15102","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_65","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_65","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_66","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_66","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide13474","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_34","si15092","si15102","Image_65","Image_66"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13474"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_14","title":"Qu’est-ce que c’est? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_39","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_39","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_40","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_40","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_43","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_43","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_44","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_44","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_19","title":"tisane ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15172","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"tisane ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15184","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"tisane ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_20","title":"croissant ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_21","title":"cafe ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_22","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_22","title":"macarons ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_23","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_23","title":"pain au chocolat ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_38","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_38","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide11458","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_14","Image_39","Image_40","Image_43","Image_44","SmartShape_19","si15172","si15184","SmartShape_20","SmartShape_21","SmartShape_22","SmartShape_23","Image_38"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":480},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide11458"}}},{"id":"si13151","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13141q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_58","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_58","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_59","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_59","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_60","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_60","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_51","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_51","title":"pain au chocolat ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13141q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13242","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si13171","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Miam-miam! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13178","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Select the ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13185hotspot","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"HotSpot_3","roles":{}},{"id":"si13185","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si13238","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si13246","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide13141q2","for":"Slide13141q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13260","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide13141q2","for":"Slide13141q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13274","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide13141q2","for":"Slide13141q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13199","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Très bien fait! You are correct - click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13141q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13212","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Désolée, you are incorrect - click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13141q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13225","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Attends! Wait! You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13141q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13141","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1703","si13151","Image_58","Image_59","Image_60","SmartShape_51","si13171","si13178","si13185","si13246","si13260","si13274","si13225"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13141"},"question":{"interactionId":"13165","quizId":377,"title":"Miam-miam!\r","text":"Select the\r","type":"graded","ikc":false,"interactionType":"hotspot","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["0"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si12969","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12959q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_56","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_56","roles":{}},{"id":"si13061","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si12990","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Un bon boisson ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12997","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Spell the name of the beverage below. Pst - it starts with a c. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13013","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13017","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si13017c","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"C\t","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si13023","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13027","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si13027c","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si13110","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13114","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si13114c","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"F","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si13121","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13125","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si13125c","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"E","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si13057","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si13065","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12959q3","for":"Slide12959q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12959q3","for":"Slide12959q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13093","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12959q3","for":"Slide12959q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13031","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Très bien fait! You are correct - click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12959q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13044","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Désolée, you are incorrect - click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12959q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12959","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1703","si12969","Image_56","si12990","si12997","si13017","si13027","si13114","si13125","si13065","si13079","si13093"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12959"},"question":{"interactionId":"12983","quizId":377,"title":"Un bon boisson\r","text":"Spell the name of the beverage below. Pst - it starts with a c.\r","type":"graded","ikc":false,"interactionType":"sequencing","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["si13017c","si13027c","si13114c","si13125c"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_30","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_30","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15114","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si15124","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_61","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_61","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide13306","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_30","si15114","si15124","Image_61"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13306"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_29","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_29","title":"Un cafe s’il-vous-plait. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12627","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_29"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":210},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12627"}}},{"id":"Image_54","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_54","roles":{}},{"id":"SmartShape_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_28","title":"Un macaron s’il-vous-plait. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12675","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_54","SmartShape_28"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":210},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12675"}}},{"id":"si12806","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12796q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_57","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_57","roles":{}},{"id":"si12898","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si12827","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Ready to order? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12834","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"How do you request the treat below? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12850","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12854","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si12854c","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Un ","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si12860","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12864","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si12864c","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"pain au chocolat","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si12947","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12951","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si12951c","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"s’il-vous-plait","index":"Not implemented"}}},{"id":"si12894","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si12902","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12796q4","for":"Slide12796q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12916","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12796q4","for":"Slide12796q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12930","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12796q4","for":"Slide12796q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12868","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Très bien fait! You are correct - click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12796q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12881","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Désolée, you are incorrect - click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide12796q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12796","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1703","si12806","Image_57","si12827","si12834","si12854","si12864","si12951","si12902","si12916","si12930"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12796"},"question":{"interactionId":"12820","quizId":377,"title":"Ready to order?\r","text":"How do you request the treat below?\r","type":"graded","ikc":false,"interactionType":"sequencing","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["si12854c","si12864c","si12951c"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si13582","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13572q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_67","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_67","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_68","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_68","roles":{}},{"id":"si13693","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si13609","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Ready to order? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13616","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"How do you request the treats below? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13631","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13635","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Un cafe et un tisane s’il-vous-plait. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13631_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Un cafe et un tisane s’il-vous-plait.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13642","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13646","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Un macaron s’il-vous-plait. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13642_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Un macaron s’il-vous-plait.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si13746","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13750","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Un cafe et un croissant s’il-vous-plait.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13746_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Un cafe et un croissant s’il-vous-plait. \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si13689","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si13697","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide13572q5","for":"Slide13572q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13711","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide13572q5","for":"Slide13572q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13725","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide13572q5","for":"Slide13572q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13650","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Très bien fait! You are correct - click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13572q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13663","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Désolée, you are incorrect - click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13572q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si13676","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Attends! Wait! You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide13572q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide13572","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1703","si13582","Image_67","Image_68","si13609","si13616","si13635","si13646","si13750","si13697","si13711","si13725","si13676"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide13572"},"question":{"interactionId":"13596","quizId":377,"title":"Ready to order?\r","text":"How do you request the treats below?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["3"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_51","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_51","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_52","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_52","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_17","title":"La Fin ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_49","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_49","title":"Aurevoir! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_50","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_50","title":"Aurevoir! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12239","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Image_51","Image_52","Text_Caption_17","SmartShape_49","SmartShape_50"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":204},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12239"}}},{"id":"Pool421","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":421,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"Le Cafe Francais","class":"project","title":"Le Cafe Francais","children":["Slide5303","Slide5375","Slide12266","Slide5506","Slide13418","Slide5621","Slide13809","Slide13976","Slide13474","Slide11458","Slide13141","Slide12959","Slide13306","Slide12627","Slide12675","Slide12796","Slide13572","Slide12239"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":377,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide13809q0","Slide13976q1","Slide13141q2","Slide12959q3","Slide12796q4","Slide13572q5"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":15,"passScore":8}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide5303","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide5375","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide12266","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide5506","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide13418","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide5621","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide13809","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide13976","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide13474","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide11458","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide13141","title":"Slide 11"},{"id":"Slide12959","title":"Slide 12"},{"id":"Slide13306","title":"Slide 13"},{"id":"Slide12627","title":"Slide 14"},{"id":"Slide12675","title":"Slide 15"},{"id":"Slide12796","title":"Slide 16"},{"id":"Slide13572","title":"Slide 17"},{"id":"Slide12239","title":"Slide 19"}]}